there to do something with that, you know, we have a young congressman that's right now
in jail for lying about where he went to college and other things. It was, you know, frankly
not good. It was pretty bad. But it was nothing compared to Blumenthal. I mean, what Blumenthal
did, he was for 20 years a hero, a great war hero. And then he sits back and, you know,
sanctimonious kind of a guy, looks down, how dare you do this to the American public, you
know. What a fake. But I thought Pam was incredible yesterday, as well as Secretary
Christine Ohm, who's really out there courageously, and I appreciate it, Christie, amazing what
you're doing. FBI Director Cash Patel, who's really coming up with some great information,
Cash. It's great. Keep it coming, because there's plenty of it. Deputy Attorney General,
one of the best lawyers you'll ever find. Todd Blanch, who I know personally is a good
lawyer, because I'm here. Thank you very much, Todd. Good job, Todd. Let me ask Attorney
General Bondi to say a few words, and then we'll follow it up with Secretary Ohm and
Director Patel, and we're going to have some of the people around the table, very courageous
people, and they're going to be talking, journalists almost all, and they're going to be talking,
and we'll take some questions from the press at the end. Okay, Pam, please. Thank you,
President Trump. And as you made clear, Antifa is a domestic left-wing terrorist organization.
We've seen them on video for years because they wanted to be seen, and they got away
with it. They beat journalists, they attack courthouses, they attack police stations,
they dox and assault our law enforcement officers. The Biden administration let them commit these
crimes with total impunity for years. So did Democrat leaders like Pritzker and Mayor
Brandon Johnson. Last week, independent journalist Nick Sorter was arrested just for protecting
himself against Antifa. I saw it online and I called Nick. I couldn't believe what happened.
He did all this just trying to save our American flag from being burned. He was pushed down
and assaulted, yet the local police arrested Nick, not the Antifa thugs who did this to
him. Antifa feels empowered to operate in the open because weak Democrats have turned
a blind eye to their actions. Their hatred for President Trump and for law and order
agendas fuels their violence. We've seen more than a thousand percent, a thousand percent
increase in attacks against our ICE agents since January 20th. Secretary Noem is out
there fighting for you firsthand to keep our federal officers safe, to keep our federal
buildings safe, and we're not going to have it anymore, these thugs. We saw what's happening
in Portland and Chicago, and you saw what happened in Dallas. No longer. This is not
activism. It's anarchy. We can't and we will not let masked terrorists burn our buildings,
attack our law enforcement, and intimidate our communities. Under your leadership, President
Trump, we're deploying the full might of the federal law enforcement to crack down on Antifa
and other domestic terrorist organizations led by Stephen Miller. And Stephen, thank
you for everything you're doing. Last week, I issued a memo ordering our federal law enforcement
agents, DEA, FBI, U.S. Marshals, and ATF to protect ICE officers from Antifa and other
radical left-wing violence. Director Patel has been going nonstop. He and Deputy Attorney
General Blanche were in Chicago yesterday. Yesterday. While Secretary Noem was in Portland,
we are around this country fighting against this domestic terrorism. We had Apple and
Google take down the ICE block apps. Hope they continue to comply with that. It's threatening
the safety of our federal law enforcement officers. We're not going to stop at just
arresting the violent criminals we can see in the streets. Fighting crime is more than
just getting the bad guy off the streets. It's breaking down the organization brick
by brick. Just like we did with cartels, we're going to take the same approach, President
Trump, with Antifa. Destroy the entire organization from top to bottom.